ammoland.com 2018-03-13

# AmmoLand Privacy Policy

**Ammoland.com Privacy Policy**  
_Our commitment to you.._

Armed Liberty AmmoLand Gun News

**USA –**  [-(Ammoland.com)- ](https://www.ammoland.com/) Ammoland is concerned about the protection of online privacy for all our website visitors. Although we track the total number of visitors to each of our sites in an aggregate form to allow us to update and improve our sites, personally identifiable information is not extracted in this process. Any cookie technology ( _where our servers deposit special codes on a visitor's computer_ ) will only be used to track non-personal information such as type of browser, operating system, and domain names to improve our visitors' online experience.

There is much confusion about cookies, how they are used, and what they can do. Cookies are very small text files written by an Internet server to a customer's browser when information is exchanged. Cookies only contain information that the server computer “ _knew_ ” in the first place and can only be read by the serving domain that placed them. Cookies are an essential part of how the Internet works today and allow server computers to recognize your computer's browser when you return.

If you have ever gone to a web page that automatically provides personalized content to you without you having to “ _log in_ ,” such as your own stock portfolio, this is almost certainly being accomplished with a cookie. As cookies are only text files, they cannot “ _run_ ” on your computer and have no ability to search your computer for other information or transmit it to anyone.

### Cookies are implemented as part of the technology implemented by your web browser.

  * For Netscape please visit : http://home.netscape.com/
  * For Microsoft please visit : http://www.microsoft.com/
  * For Firefox please visit : https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/products/firefox/protect-your-privacy/cookies
  * For Chrome please visit : https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en

Ammoland only collects personally identifiable data, such as names, addresses, email addresses, and the like, when voluntarily submitted by a visitor. In addition, we advise minors to get parental permission before filling out any online forms.

Ammoland does not sell or release any information gathered on our websites to any third parties unless given permission to do so. All information gathered online will be used only by Ammoland for internal marketing analysis and to improve our products, services and websites.

### In the event Ammoland is operating with network based advertisers user should be aware:

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

In some instances, when an email address has been provided by the visitor, and the visitor is 18 or older and has indicated that he/she would like to receive communications from us, we will send notices to visitors, usually in the form of an email.

These notices, sent periodically, will announce website upgrades, new product information, daily or monthly subscription emails and other similar updates.

### Email Privacy Policy:

This email privacy policy demonstrates Ammoland’s firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of the address you provided when you subscribed to the email notification feature of this blog.

Why did you receive an email from Ammoland?

If you received an email from Ammoland, that means that your email address is listed in the system because you have expressly shared it for the purpose of receiving information on the website’s content. All email subscriptions in our database are _“double-opt-in_ ” in nature. That means that the recipient of the email notifications not only has requested the subscription, but has additionally confirmed the subscription request by clicking a link on a confirmation email sent by Ammoland.

> ### In short you subscribed to us and confirmed it. If you don't want our emails you can unsubscribe at anytime on this page: <https://www.ammoland.com/subscribe/>

### Ammoland Protects Your Privacy:

Ammoland uses strict security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data used by the subscription system.

### Sharing and Usage?

NEVER, under any circumstance, will AmmoLand share, sell, or rent individual personal information to anyone, unless ordered to do so by a court of law. Information submitted to Ammoland is available to Ammoland staff of this site for the express purpose of contacting you based on your request for information and notifications of new blog content.

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time without notifying guests of the existence of a new privacy policy.

[](http://monitor4.sucuri.net/verify.php?r=bc15b0fe288720de9dd7309ee00ad9b95cca42f6a7)Sucuri

© 2015 AmmoLand.com – All Rights Reserved.
